Delmy Melendez

Profile

I have 5 years in customer service management, with leading a department of my own. Able to train others and learn from others as well. Highly professional with extensive training in computer programs, and customer service techniques. Comfortable in a fast paced environment, exceptionally fast learner.

Contact

M | 435.513.1099

E | delmymm93@gmail.com

L | 598 N 250 W, Heber City, UT 84032

Skills

- Great organization skills
- Possess great knowledge in Microsoft Word and Excel
- Adapt to diverse groups
- Problem solving skills
- Professional demeanor
- Interpersonal skills
- High energy
- Social perceptiveness
- Bilingual (English and Spanish)

Education

High School Diploma

Wasatch High School Heber City, UT 2011

References

Stephany Perez, 435.513.1753

Kiara Lopez, 801.455.3058

Coral Gramse, 385.424.2328

Professional Experience

October 2019 - Present Chartsquad, Pursuit Member

- Possess knowledge of HIPAA and HITECH federal laws
- Data entry
- Make calls to providers office, each handled uniquely to request
- Made payments
- Determined how to effectively handle situations when problems arose
- Fulfilled each client's needs to the best of my ability

May 2019 - October 2019 Leavitt Group Insurance Agency, Customer Service Representative

- Gather personal information to quote clients
- Relay information to other staff members, so questions are handled in a timely manner
- Answer calls and emails
- Collect all forms of payment for policies
- Collect and sort through all mail so it reaches correct member
- Create and send out all types of insurance certificates, ID cards, etc.

October 2016 - Present One Stop House Cleaning, Administrative Assistant

- Answer all calls, texts, emails
- Track employee hours worked on Excel
- File all documents received
- Worked collaboratively in a team environment
- Developed positive customer relationships through friendly meetings and customer service
- Prioritized and accomplished wide range of tasks each shift
- Resolved all customer complaints in a professional manner while prioritizing the customer

Delmy Melendez

November 2013 - October 2017 All Resort Group, Guest Services Manager

- Wrote company memos on various policies
- Organized and prepared all cubicles to ensure agents had all needed
- Answered customer calls promptly in an appropriate manner
- Asked open ended questions to assess customers needs
- Processed cash and credit card payments rapidly and accurately
- Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathic manner